<resources>
	<string name="app_name">WiFi Better Battery</string>
	<string name="action_wifi">WiFi Manager</string>
	<string name="action_networks">Networks</string>
	<string name="action_refresh">Scan</string>
	<string name="nActionConnect">Connect once</string>
	<string name="nActionAdd">Auto connect</string>
	<string name="nActionDisconnect">Disconnect</string>
	<string name="nActionRemove">Disable auto connect</string>
	<string name="undo">Undo</string>
	<string name="widgetDescription">Toggles automatic WiFi management</string>

	<string name="wifiLevel">Connection quality</string>
	<string name="wifiConnected">Connected</string>
	<string name="wifiEmpty">No networks have been found.</string>
	<string name="newMac">
		You are connecting to this network for the first time!
		\nThe router\'s MAC address is %s. If possible, please verify it.
		\nDon\'t be concerned that you are seeing this notification - it is only shown as a security mechanism.
		\nIf you are certain that you are connecting to the correct network, you can just tap \"Connect\".
		\nYou can disable this warning in Settings.
	</string>
	<string name="macChanged">
		The router\'s MAC address has changed!
		\nThis could mean that another network is pretending to be the network %1$s!
		\nThis notification could also be shown if: 1) The network\'s router was replaced. 2) A network is using multiple routers.
		\nThe unknown MAC address is %2$s.
		\nYou can disable this warning in Settings.
	</string>
	<string name="macAdd">Add MAC address to known ones for this network</string>
	<string name="macDontConnect">Don\'t connect</string>
	<string name="networksEmpty">No networks have been saved yet!</string>
	<string name="macsEmpty">No MAC addresses are known for this network yet!</string>
	<string name="networkDeleted">Network deleted: %s</string>
	<string name="macDeleted">MAC deleted: %s</string>
	<string name="connectingTo">Connecting to %s</string>
	<string name="networkUnknown">
		You do not have connection data stored for this network yet.
		\nWhen you tap Okay, Android\'s settings utility will be opened.
		\nPlease connect to the network there.
	</string>

	<string name="macQuestion"><![CDATA[
		Would you like to activate MAC checks?<br />
		By default, Android <i>only</i> checks the name of a network before connecting to it.<br />
		That means that if you have a network saved, and Android detects another network with the same name, Android automatically tries to connect to it.<br />
		A malicious device could use this to collect passwords or send harmful data to your device.<br />
		Checking it thus helps verify a network\'s identity.<br />
		It is strongly recommended that you enable this, but it means a few additional warnings will be shown.
	]]></string>
	<string name="compatibilityModeActive">Legacy mode activated instead. You can change this in settings.</string>
	
	<string name="prefCatWifi">WiFi</string>
	<string name="prefRefreshTime">Refresh interval</string>
	<string name="prefRefreshTimeDesc">The amount of time between checking whether a network is in range. The smaller the interval, the quicker you will be connected, but the more battery is used!</string>
	<string name="prefMacCheck">MAC check</string>
	<string name="prefMacCheckDesc">This is an optional security feature. Check the help for more information.</string>
	<string name="prefAutoFuncs">Automatic WiFi management</string>
	<string name="prefAutoFuncsDesc">Automatically switch WiFi off and connect to known networks. Required to save battery!</string>
	<string name="prefLegacy">Legacy auto-scan mode</string>
	<string name="prefLegacyDesc">Use legacy scanning mode instead of low-power states. Activate this if you see high power usage. No effect &lt; Android 4.3. See help for more info.</string>
	<string name="prefCatPlan">Planning</string>
	<string name="prefPlanEnabled">Enable planning</string>
	<string name="prefPlanEnabledDesc">Switch WiFi auto-control off between Start time and End time.</string>
	<string name="prefPlanStart">Start time</string>
	<string name="prefPlanEnd">End time</string>
	<string name="prefDisableScreenOff">Disable with screen off</string>
	<string name="prefDisableScreenOffDesc">Disable WiFi when the screen of your device is turned off to save even more battery.</string>

	<string name="macNotifTitle">MAC change detected!</string>
	<string name="macNotifText">The network %s was found, but no connection was established because its MAC address changed. Please tap here for options.</string>

	<string-array name="refreshTimeNames">
		<item>30 seconds</item>
		<item>1 minute</item>
		<item>2 minutes</item>
		<item>3 minutes</item>
		<item>5 minutes</item>
		<item>10 minutes</item>
		<item>Custom…</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="timePickerMinutes">Minutes</string>

	<string-array name="help_spinner">
		<item>General</item>
		<item>@string/action_wifi</item>
		<item>@string/action_networks</item>
		<item>@string/action_settings</item>
	</string-array>

	<string-array name="help_texts">
		<item><![CDATA[
			<h1>Permissions</h1>
			The permissions which WiFi Better Battery requests on your device have been chosen with great care. All permissions are necessary for its full functionality.<br />
			Just in case you still have concerns we have listed all requested permissions below, each with an explanation of why we need it.<br /><br />
			<b>Network permissions:</b> Necessary to list all available networks and to connect to networks.<br />
			<b>Internet:</b> Used only for Google ads.<br />
		]]></item>
		<item><![CDATA[
			<h1>List of networks</h1>
			After opening the app, the first thing you see is the list of available networks. WiFi does not have to be turned on for this function.<br />
			You can see the names and signal strengths of the networks here. When you tap on a network, the options for it are displayed.
			<h1>Warnings</h1>
			If the MAC check is enabled in the Settings, you may get a warning when connecting. For more information please consult the \"Networks\" help.<br />
			For connection problems, please follow the instructions offered by the Android system settings.
		]]></item>
		<item><![CDATA[
			This function is mainly relevant if the MAC check is enabled in the Settings (recommended!).
			<h1>MAC check</h1>
			The MAC check is an added check whether the network you want to connect to is actually the one you think it is.<br />
			By default, Android <i>only</i> checks the name of a network before connecting to it.<br />
			That means that if you have a network saved, and Android detects another network with the same name, Android automatically tries to connect to it.<br />
			A malicious device could use this to collect passwords that are sent during connection attempts or send harmful data to your device.<br />
			A MAC address uniquely identifies a device.
			<h1>How it works</h1>
			When connecting to a network and when the MAC check is on, Wifi Better Battery automatically checks whether the MAC address is known for this network.<br />
			In \"Networks\" you can delete known networks and MAC addresses that you have added at an earlier time.
		]]></item>
		<item><![CDATA[
			<h1>General</h1>
		    <b>Language:</b> You can change the application language here.<br />
		    <b>Show ads:</b> Please consider supporting us by activating unobstrusive ads here.<br />
		    <b>Theme:</b> Here you can change whether the app uses light or dark colours.<br />
		    <b>Drawer open on start:</b> Activate this to have the navigation drawer on the left be open when you start the app. Has no effect on tablets, as the drawer is always open on tablets.
		    <h1>WiFi</h1>
		    <b>Refresh interval:</b> This settings controls how often Wifi Better Battery scans for networks. The lower this setting is, the quicker WiFi will be enabled when you get in range of a known network, but the higher the battery usage will be.<br />
		    <b>MAC check:</b> Here you can disable the MAC check before a connection attempt (not recommended!). For more information about this feature please consult the \"Networks\" help.<br />
		    <b>Automatic WiFi management:</b> If you turn off this option, all automatic functions of WiFi Better Battery are disabled - it will not automatically turn off WiFi or connect you to saved networks anymore. This means it cannot save battery either! The widget toggles this setting.
			<b>Legacy auto-scan mode:</b> In Android >= 4.3 auto-scan is implemented by keeping WiFi in a low-power mode, which is more efficient than turning it off and on all the time. On some devices, this feature is broken and it uses full power anyway. Activate this to be able to save power on such a device. If you activate it, please disable the "Scanning always available" option in your device\'s advanced WiFi settings. This setting has no effect on Android < 4.3.
			<h1>Planning</h1>
			<b>Enable Planning:</b> This setting, and the <b>Start time</b> and <b>End time</b> settings can be used to make WiFi Better Battery stop managing WiFi at certain times, for instance during the night.
			<b>Disable with screen off:</b> To save even more battery, you can enable this setting so WiFi is turned off when your screen is turned off. This function does not check for active downloads.
	]]></item>
	</string-array>

	<string name="dialogConnect">Connect</string>
</resources>